<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WoW on GTKer.com</title><link>https://gtker.com/tags/wow/</link><description>Recent content in WoW on GTKer.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>contact@gtker.com (Gtker)</managingEditor><webMaster>contact@gtker.com (Gtker)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gtker.com/tags/wow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Implementation Guide for the World of Warcraft PIN calculation</title><link>https://gtker.com/implementation-guide-for-the-world-of-warcraft-pin-calculation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>contact@gtker.com (Gtker)</author><guid>https://gtker.com/implementation-guide-for-the-world-of-warcraft-pin-calculation/</guid><description>Starting with client version 1.12 the user can enter a PIN which is hashed and sent to the server. This post details how the client calculates the hash for World of Warcraft 1.12 and provides replication values in order to test your own implementation.
Background The server may send a PIN grid seed and PIN salt in CMD_AUTH_LOGON_CHALLENGE_Server (wiki) if it chooses. The client may send the PIN salt and client PIN hash in CMD_AUTH_LOGON_PROOF_Client (wiki) in the field just after the client proof.</description></item><item><title>Implementation Guide for the World of Warcraft client integrity check</title><link>https://gtker.com/implementation-guide-for-the-world-of-warcraft-client-integrity-check/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>contact@gtker.com (Gtker)</author><guid>https://gtker.com/implementation-guide-for-the-world-of-warcraft-client-integrity-check/</guid><description>When an original World of Warcraft client (1.2 through to 3.3.5) authenticates with the server the client will send a hash of some local game files. This post details how the client calculates the hash for World of Warcraft 1.12 and provides replication values in order to test your own implementation.
Background The server sends a checksum salt in CMD_AUTH_LOGON_CHALLENGE_Server in the field just after the SRP6 salt. The client sends the final hash in CMD_AUTH_LOGON_PROOF_Client in the field just after the client proof.</description></item><item><title>Implementation Guide for the World of Warcraft flavor of SRP6</title><link>https://gtker.com/implementation-guide-for-the-world-of-warcraft-flavor-of-srp6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>contact@gtker.com (Gtker)</author><guid>https://gtker.com/implementation-guide-for-the-world-of-warcraft-flavor-of-srp6/</guid><description>The authentication protocol for authenticating with a World of Warcraft (WoW) server is widely available but not very well documented. Most documentation is spread across forums or just directly links to RFC2945, the 8 page, 20 year old, very broad and unspecific RFC that describes SRP6 in relatively academic terms.
The goal of this article is to be an approachable, complete guide to implementing the protocol specifically for WoW 1.12 without requiring external references.</description></item></channel></rss>